Edwin Diamond Political Audiovisual Collection
Edwin Diamond Political Audiovisual Collection
- Tapes D0300-D0599
  - D0507 USA/USSR Spacebridge: The Role of Media in Current Relations - Producer: Center for Communication, 7/1/87 (Box 27)
  - D0508 Political Ads - Producer: Ch. 4, 11/13 - 14/?? (Box 27)
  - D0509 Jimmy Baldwin - Producer: Channel 13, 3/11/83 (Box 27)
  - D0510 Gay March'93: What You Didn't See on Network TV - Producer: Christian Action Network (Box 27)
  - D0511 Flag Protection Ad - Massachusetts - Producer: Citizens Flag Alliance, 10/4/86 (Box 27)
  - D0512 [no title] (Box 27)
  - D0513 Morning News/Nightly News - Producer: CNN/NBC, 11/6 - 7/85 (Box 27)
  - D0514 Project - Gorby from Geneva - Producer: CNN, 11/21/85 (Box 27)
  - D0515 Moneyline - Producer: CNN, 10/20/87 (Box 28)
  - D0516 NY Primary / Penn. Primary - - Producer: CNN, 4/19/88; 4/26/88 (Box 28)
  - D0517 World Report - with Piece on 1990 Campaign Ads in Use Around the Country - Producer: CNN, 10/3/90 (Box 28)
  - D0518 Prisoners of the Game - Camp #1 - 3 - Producer: CNN, 10/18/90 (Box 28)
  - D0519 Prisoners of the Game - Camp #4 - Producer: CNN, 10/18/90 (Box 28)
  - D0520 Savings & Loan / Ken Bode #1 & 2 - Producer: CNN, 10/18/90 (Box 28)
  - D0521 Savings & Loan / Ken Bode #3 & 4 - - Producer: CNN, 10/18/90 (Box 28)
  - D0522 Special Assignment The Invasion File - Producer: CNN, 10/25/90 (Box 28)
  - D0523 No Code - Producer: CNN, 1/18/91 (Box 28)
  - D0524 Rocketts - Today Show / Political Spots / New Hampshire Primary / Letterman Prime Time Special - Producer: CNN/C - SPAN/NBC, 12/95; 2/96 (Box 28)
  - D0525 [no title] (Box 28)
  - D0526 [no title] (Box 28)
  - D0527 Moneyline - Producer: CNN, 10/19/?? (Box 28)
  - D0528 Moneyline - Producer: CNN, 10/20/?? (Box 28)
  - D0529 President Bush Special - Producer: CNN, 5/24/?? (Box 28)
  - D0530 Special Assignment - Democracy in America: The Pillars of our Prosperity - Producer: CNN, 9/27/?? (Box 28)
  - D0531 Special Assignment - Democracy in America - A Government for the People - - Producer: CNN, 10/4/?? (Box 28)
  - D0532 Evening News - Daybreak - Prime News - Producer: CNN/NBC, 11/8,9,10,18/?? (Box 28)
  - D0533 Prime News / Daybreak / Nightly News - Producer: CNN/NBC, 11/18 - 20/?? (Box 28)
  - D0534 Daybreak, Primenews - Producer: CNN, 11/21 - 22/?? (Box 28)
  - D0535 SAS - The Nation's Agenda - A House Divided - Producer: CNN (Box 28)
  - D0536 Special Assignment - Freedom for Sale: Bail Bond Special - Producer: CNN (Box 28)
  - D0537 Special Assignment - Hollywood and Politics - Brooks Jackson - Producer: CNN (Box 28)
  - D0538 Special Assignment - The General's Price: The Full Story - Producer: CNN (Box 28)
  - D0539 Borders - by Merrill Aldighieri & Joe Tripivan - Producer: Co - Directions Inc, 1989 (Box 28)
  - D0540 Indecision 92: The Republican National Convention - Producer: Comedy Central, 8/18/92 (Box 28)
  - D0541 Search for Common Ground on Abortion - Producer: Common Ground Productions (Box 28)
  - D0542 84 Spots - Election Eve (RR WM) - Producer: Cranston for President (Box 28)
  - D0543 The Lincoln/Douglas Debates - Producer: C - Span, 8/20/94 (Box 28)
  - D0544 Cityscope - Host Robert Hirschfield - Guest Seigi Hinata, James Shields - Producer: CUNY - TV, 2/19/92 (Box 28)
  - D0545 New Commercials - Producer: Daily News (Box 28)
  - D0546 Promo - Long Version - Trump: What's the Deal - Producer: Deadline Company, 6/22/89 (Box 28)
  - D0547 George Orwell's Animal Farm 1954/1986 - Producer: deRochemont Films Inc./Vestron Inc. (Box 28)
  - D0548 Hands Across America - Producer: DHS Films, 4/18/86 (Box 28)
  - D0549 Bob Dole: An American Hero - Producer: Dole for President Inc., 1995 (Box 28)
  - D0550 Volume 1 Show 14 - Producer: Dreyfus Roundtable, The, 4/14/89 (Box 28)
  - D0551 Olympia Dukakis - Convention Intro and Home Movie - Producer: Dukakis for President (Box 28)
  - D0552 C - Span off Air - ESI Gatt Panel - Producer: Economic Strategy Institute (Box 28)
  - D0553 TV Campaign Spot - Producer: Eisenhower for President, 1952 (Box 28)
  - D0554 Dukakis for President - "Jimmy" - Producer: Evans / McNamara (Box 28)
  - D0555 Presidential Primary Campaign Spots - Producer: Fanna - Diamond, 1992 (Box 28)
  - D0556 FNN Power Profile - Peter W. Eldredge - U.S. Publisher Newsweek Magazine - Producer: FNN, 3/5/91 (Box 28)
  - D0557 B12 Study - Producer: FNN (Box 28)
  - D0558 Time (Revised) - Producer: Forbes (Box 28)
  - D0559 Tax Cut / Bio Vision - Producer: Forbes for President (Box 29)
  - D0560 Term Limits May Cancel / Term Limits Cancelled - Producer: Forbes for President (Box 29)
  - D0561 Entertainment News / Style News - Producer: Fox (Box 29)
  - D0562 Style News - WWD, Calvin Klein, Couture, Dress for Defense, Neal Slavin - Producer: Fox (Box 29)
  - D0563 Handcuffed Reporting - Classroom Version - Producer: Freedom Forum, 10/26/94 (Box 29)
  - D0564 Nukes - Producer: Frontline, 11/19/96 (Box 29)
  - D0565 The Press, The Presidency & The First Hundred Days Tape #2 - Producer: Gannett Center for Media Studies, 1/23/89 (Box 29)
  - D0566 The Press, the Presidency, and the First Hundred Days - Press Conference - Producer: Gannett Center for Media Studies, 1/23/89 (Box 29)
  - D0567 The Press, the Presidency, and the First Hundred Days Tape #3 - Producer: Gannett Center for Media Studies, 1/23/89 (Box 29)
  - D0568 The Gannett Decades - Producer: Gannett Co. Inc. (Box 29)
  - D0569 Tackle - Producer: Great American Media Inc. Clinton for President, 2/26/92 (Box 29)
  - D0570 Time - Producer: Great American Media Inc. Clinton for President, 2/27/92 (Box 29)
  - D0571 Page - Producer: Great American Media Inc. Clinton for President, 3/10/92 (Box 29)
  - D0572 Commitment - Producer: Great American Media Inc. Clinton for President, 3/12/92 (Box 29)
  - D0573 Triple Play - Producer: Great American Media Inc. Clinton for President, 3/12/92 (Box 29)
  - D0574 Which - Producer: Great American Media Inc. Clinton for President, 3/20/92 (Box 29)
  - D0575 Aired Spots - General Election - Producer: Great American Media Inc. C1inton/Gore '92, 9/30/92 (Box 29)
  - D0576 General Election Aired Spot Compilation Reel - Producer: Great American Media Inc. Clinton/Gore'92, 10/12/92 (Box 29)
  - D0577 Tanner'88: The Dark Horse - Producer: HBO, 2/8/88 (Box 29)
  - D0578 The Image - Producer: HBO, 11/27/89 (Box 29)
  - D0579 My Mother's Murder - Producer: HBO (Box 29)
  - D0580 Free Speech & Advertising - Who Draws the Line? - Producer: Institute for Democratic Communication at Boston University, 1/9/87 (Box 29)
  - D0581 Star*Pac "1st Choice 88: The President and the Arms Race" - Producer: IPBN TV, 9/27/87 (Box 29)
  - D0582 D C Divided City - Producer: Koppel Communications Inc., 5/5/89 (Box 29)
  - D0583 D.C. - Divided City? - Part II - Producer: Koppel Communications Inc., 5/5/89 (Box 29)
  - D0584 Bob Hope - Science Notes - Producer: KQED - TV - San Francisco, CA, 1988 (Box 29)
  - D0585 The ANC & South Africa - Producer: Kwitny Report, The, 2/11/87 (Box 29)
  - D0586 Special - The Assassination of JFK - Producer: Kwitny Report, The (Box 29)
  - D0587 Colorado Ranch, Red Square, GAK Seminar in MW - Producer: L. Mosher Film (Box 29)
  - D0588 Nightshift Boston ABC, WCVB - TV, MIT Show - Producer: Linda Kun (Box 29)
  - D0589 Political 60's - Producer: London International Advertising Awards (Box 29)
  - D0590 Political 80's - Producer: London International Advertising Awards (Box 29)
  - D0591 Episode 5: Picking up the Pieces / Episode 6: Legacy of the Sixties - Producer: Making Sense of the Sixties, 1/24/91 (Box 29)
  - D0592 TAB - Car Wash, Library, Football - Producer: McCann/Erickson - Coca Cola USA (Box 29)
  - D0593 A Generation Under the Gun - Producer: MTV News, 12/9/93 (Box 29)
  - D0594 Facing the Future with Bill Clinton - Producer: MTV News (Box 29)
  - D0595 Facing the Future with Bill Clinton - Producer: MTV News (Box 29)
  - D0596 Hot City (Group w Satellite Media Production Dept.) - Producer: Nashville Network (Box 29)
  - D0597 A Stitch in Time: Saving the Last Great Places - Producer: Nature Conservatory, The, 1992 (Box 29)
  - D0598 News Tape - Tues - Sat. 8 - Producer: NBC, Case says 1984 (Box 29)
  - D0599 News - Summit Coverage - Producer: NBC, 11/11 - 21/85 (Box 29)
- Tapes D0600-D0899
  - D0600 [no title] - Producer: NBC, 1/7 - 9/87 (Box 29)
  - D0601 [no title] - Producer: NBC, 1/11 - 13/87 (Box 30)
  - D0602 [no title] - Producer: NBC, 1/14 - 17/87 (Box 30)
  - D0603 [no title] - Producer: NBC, 1/19 - 20/87 (Box 30)
  - D0604 [no title] - Producer: NBC, 1/21 - 24/87 (Box 30)
  - D0605 [no title] - Producer: NBC, 1/25 - 2/8/87 (Box 30)
  - D0606 [no title] - Producer: NBC, 1/29 - 2/1/87 (Box 30)
  - D0607 [no title] - Producer: NBC, 12/2 - 4/87 (Box 30)
  - D0608 [no title] - Producer: NBC, 2/5 - 7/87 (Box 30)
  - D0609 [no title] - Producer: NBC, 12/8 - 10/87 (Box 30)
  - D0610 Tower Commission Report - Producer: NBC, 2/26/87 (Box 30)
  - D0611 [no title] - Producer: NBC, 4/12 - 14/87 (Box 30)
  - D0612 [no title] - Producer: NBC, 4/15 - 18/87 (Box 30)
  - D0613 Morning News - Producer: NBC, 5/27/88 (Box 30)
  - D0614 Today Show - Moscow Summit Coverage - Producer: NBC, 5/30 - 31/88 (Box 30)
  - D0615 Moscow Summit - Producer: NBC, 5/31/88 (Box 30)
  - D0616 Morning News - Producer: NBC, 6/2/88 (Box 30)
  - D0617 Nightly News - Producer: NBC, 4/17 - 5/24/89 (Box 30)
  - D0618 NATO - boat wavin[?] etc. "Giddy" "S. Ohara" - Producer: NBC, 5/31/89 (Box 30)
  - D0619 Super bowl XXVI (includes ads) - Clinton - Producer: NBC, 1/27/92 (Box 30)
  - D0620 Advertising Segment (Ross Perot) - Today Program News - Producer: NBC, 6/5/92 (Box 30)
  - D0621 Media Relations Today Show - Perot - Producer: NBC, 6/11/92 (Box 30)
  - D0622 Media Relations - Today: Perot - Producer: NBC, 10/5/92 (Box 30)
  - D0623 Brokaw - A Day at the White House - Producer: NBC, 5/7/93 (Box 30)
  - D0624 Entertainment - TV Nation/Premiere "Rough Cut" - Producer: NBC, 7/19/94 (Box 30)
  - D0625 Today: Ad Watch - Diamond / Maja Holkeboer - Producer: NBC, 10/24 - 30/?? (Box 30)
  - D0626 Alerdnick Press Coverage - Vremya Summit Coverage - Producer: NBC, 11/19/?? (Box 30)
  - D0627 Dateline - USSR/USA Maryland Public TV (Maryland Spacebridge) - Producer: NBC (Box 30)
  - D0628 Media Relations - "Today" in Africa - Highlights - Producer: NBC (Box 30)
  - D0629 Nightly News: Gorby - Producer: NBC (Box 30)
  - D0630 Nukes for Beginners / Checkers ET / Red News - Producer: NBC (Box 30)
  - D0631 Politics '80: JC / Hostage / Bush - Producer: NBC (Box 30)
  - D0632 Edison - Producer: New York Times, 8/15/90 (Box 30)
  - D0633 World Comm #2080 Paper of Record - Producer: New York Times (Box 30)
  - D0634 Mike Norman - Producer: New York Times Magazine (Box 30)
  - D0635 Campaign '88 #4 - Producer: Nightline, 9/26/88 (Box 30)
  - D0636 Keeping America #l: Business & Presidential Leadership - Producer: Nightly Business Report & Fortune, The, 1992 (Box 30)
  - D0637 1990 Fantasy Campaign - Producer: Nissan Motor Corp. in USA (Box 30)
  - D0638 The Network Story - Producer: NTA (ABC, CBS, NBC) (Box 30)
  - D0639 Massaging the Media - Preview Copy 2 - Producer: On the Issues, 1994, season 2 (Box 30)
  - D0640 Demo Reel - Producer: Payne & Company, 5/31/89 (Box 30)
  - D0641 10 Spots - Producer: Payne & Company - Dukakis for President (Box 30)
  - D0642 Homeless, Healthcare, MediCare - Producer: Payne & Company - Dukakis for President (Box 30)
  - D0643 Long Bio, Short Bio, Contra, Bowl - Producer: Payne & Company - Dukakis for President (Box 30)
  - D0644 American Game, Japanese Rules - Producer: PBS, 4/26/88 (Box 30)
  - D0645 Special - Japan - Producer: PBS, 10/23/90 (Box 31)
  - D0646 Special - Campaign Stenzier 10/22/?? - Producer: PBS (Box 31)
  - D0647 Television Selected Programs - Producer: PBS (Box 31)
  - D0648 Productions Pets or Meat The Return to Flint - Producer: PDR (Box 31)
  - D0649 Computer/Bob Michel - Producer: Philip Stern Citizens for Common Sense (Box 31)
  - D0650 Gennifer Flowers - 'Run and Hide' - Producer: Presidential Victory Committee, 7/9/92 (Box 31)
  - D0651 Bride - Producer: Presidential Victory Committee, 10/14/92 (Box 31)
  - D0652 Moyers: The Secret Government - The Constitution in Crisis - Producer: Pub114 Affairs Television, 11/4/87 (Box 31)
  - D0653 Listening to America with Bill Moyers - "The Money Trail" #124 - Producer: Public Affairs Television, 10/6/92 (Box 31)
  - D0654 The Great Healthcare Debate - Producer: Public Affairs Television, 10/7/94 (Box 31)
  - D0655 Coffee Achievers - Producer: Radio TV Reports Inc. (Box 31)
  - D0656 Scoundrel - Producer: Radio TV Reports Inc. (Box 31)
  - D0657 The Wall Comes Down - Producer: Reuters Ltd., 1990 (Box 31)
  - D0658 Broken Promises - Producer: River Bank Inc. Buchanan for President, 2/4/92 (Box 31)
  - D0659 An Introduction to Rosenfeld, Sirowitz & Lawson - Producer: Rosenfeld, Sirowitz & Lawson, Inc. (Box 31)
  - D0660 Money Politics - Producer: Ruder - Finn, 4/6/92 (Box 31)
  - D0661 Senator Moynihan Campaign '88 - Producer: Sawyer Miller Group, 1988 (Box 31)
  - D0662 Compare - Koch Kemp - Dishes - Office - Reality - Producer: Senator D'Amato Campaign (Box 31)
  - D0663 Showtime 30 Minute Movie - Producer: Showtime, 7/23/90 (Box 31)
  - D0664 Roger & Me - Producer: TJT Documentaries (Box 31)
  - D0665 Guerrilla Media 3 Sections - Producer: Tony Schwartz (Box 31)
  - D0666 How I Use Media in Politics - Producer: Tony Schwartz (Box 31)
  - D0667 Four More Years 1991 - Producer: Top Value Television Classics, 1972 (Box 31)
  - D0668 Swin, Leadership, Taking Control, Emergency, Change, Alone, Russ, Difference - Producer: Tsongas for President - Shea/Woods Productions, 1/6 - 2/20/92 (Box 31)
  - D0669 Woods/Shea "Leadership" - Producer: Tsongas for President Committee, 1/6/92 (Box 31)
  - D0670 Change / Emergency - Producer: Tsongas for President Committee, 2/1/92 (Box 31)
  - D0671 Reagan '84 Commercials - Producer: Tuesday Team, 1984 (Box 31)
  - D0672 Reagan Commercials - Producer: Tuesday Team, 1984 (Box 31)
  - D0673 The People for 0'Rourke - Andrew 0'Rouke 11 Spots - Producer: Tuesday Team, 9/5/86 (Box 31)
  - D0674 The Nuclear Graveyard - Producer: Turner Broadcasting, 6/14/91 (Box 31)
  - D0675 Special Assignment Assault Weapons - Producer: Tylie Jones East, 3/14/91 (Box 31)
  - D0676 The Television Show - Program Master - Producer: USA Today, 10/20/88 (Box 31)
  - D0677 Frontline - Who Profits from Drugs - #706 - Producer: WGBH (Box 31)
  - D0678 Made in America?: Cars/Electronics - Producer: WGBH (Box 31)
  - D0679 Made in America?: Program 1 & 2 - Pix Lock/Planes/Clothes - Producer: WGBH (Box 31)
  - D0680 John Rhodes - Producer: Wm Paterson College (Box 31)
  - D0681 Strictly Business Sales Presentation - Producer: WNBC - TV, 1/5/86 (Box 31)
  - D0682 Independent Focus - Producer: WNET/Thirteen, 7/19/88 (Box 31)
  - D0683 Independent Focus - Producer: WNET/Thirteen, 7/19/88 (Box 31)
  - D0684 Inside Albany - Host Lise Bang - Jensen, Guest Seigi Hinata - Producer: WNET/Thirteen, 9/15/91 (Box 31)
  - D0685 Charlie Rose - Guest Seigi Hinata, Richard Holbrooke, Walter Shapiro - Producer: WNET/Thirteen, 2/5/92 (Box 31)
  - D0686 Eastenders - Producer: WNYC - TV/31 (Box 31)
  - D0687 More Than Broken Glass: Memories of Kristallnacht - Producer: WNYC - TV/31 (Box 31)
  - D0688 Inside Channel 9 - Producer: WWOR - TV, 2/21/88 (Box 31)
  - D0689 Independent Committee of Ethics Political Action Committee - Producer: Zimmerman & Markman, 10/1/92 (Box 31)
  - D0690 Choice (revised) - Producer: Zimmerman & Markman, 10/15/92 (Box 32)
  - D0691 War Comes to America, 1944? (Box 32)
  - D0692 The Candidate: Harlan County, 1976 (Box 32)
  - D0693 Cronkite (Diamond WNET) (Box 32)
  - D0694 Canadian Election Nite / JC / KFC (Box 32)
  - D0695 Campaign '80, 1980 (Box 32)
  - D0696 Campaign '80 NH Primary - FL/IL/NY/PA (Box 32)
  - D0697 Campaign '80: Reagan Anderson Debate / JFK Memorials / Reagan Hi Frontier (Box 32)
  - D0698 Politics '80: R. Reagan, EM Kennedy w/Mudd CBS Bush Bio, 1980 (Box 32)
  - D0699 Various Political Commercials (Best CX CX of All Time), 1992; CX might stand for commercials (Box 32)
  - D0700 [no title] (Box 32)
  - D0701 Campaign '82 California: Wilson/Brown Debate / Brown Spots / Best Cx Cx NBC (Box 32)
  - D0702 84 Election Eve/Night/Post: Spots/Coverage/Highlights (Box 32)
  - D0703 John Glenn Ads / Jesse Helms / Jim Hunt / N. Carolina Race (Box 32)
  - D0704 Politics '84 - Ed on NBC, Reagan Docu., 20/20 Ed Ads, Reagan, '84 Spots, 1984 (Box 32)
  - D0705 Campaign '92 - '84 Debate, 1984 - 1992; case has '96 GOP/NH (Box 32)
  - D0706 John Henning Campaign '84 Special/ Atomic Café, 2/26/84 (Box 32)
  - D0707 1984 Political Campaign, Spots, Championship Figure Skating, Cabbage Patch Christmas, To Be or Not To Be, 12/13/84; date given on enclosed note (Box 32)
  - D0708 Beyond War Spacebridge Highlights / Vremya News Story / WNBC / RR / Ferraro, 12/13 - 15/84 (Box 32)
  - D0709 Michael O'Keefe 17.255 Monitoring Project, 12/14/84 (Box 32)
  - D0710 Christmas Adventures of Karl Bertil Johnson, 1985 (Box 32)
  - D0711 World News Tonight, 11/4 - 6/85 (Box 32)
  - D0712 News Study Group - CBS National News (am & pm), 11/6 - 8/85 (Box 32)
  - D0713 News Study Group - Harvey Milk Documentary, 11/8/85 (Box 32)
  - D0714 Summit Coverage - Reagan, Gorbatschow in Genf #1, 11/17 - 20/85 (Box 32)
  - D0715 Summit Coverage - Reagan, Gorbatschow in Genf #2, 11/18 - 21/85 (Box 32)
  - D0716 Summit Coverage - Final Day, 11/21/85 (Box 32)
  - D0717 Douglas Davis - Ménage a Trois, 1986 (Box 32)
  - D0718 N - N South African Segs, 1/1/86 (Box 32)
  - D0719 60 Minutes - Ted Turner, 4/20/86 (Box 32)
  - D0720 Morning News 7 - 9AM, 5/6/86 (Box 32)
  - D0721 Sixty Minutes: Donald Trump, 6/29/86 (Box 32)
  - D0722 48 Hours an Crack Street, 9/2/86 (Box 32)
  - D0723 Puzzle Weekend Pilot, 10/31/87 (Box 32)
  - D0724 88 Political Ads - Babbitt, Dukakis, Dole, Kemp, Bush - Diamond Copy, 1988 (Box 32)
  - D0725 '88 Political Spots, 1988 (Box 32)
  - D0726 88 Prez. Race - Election Eve, 1988 (Box 32)
  - D0727 88 Spots - Prez. Race, 1988 (Box 32)
  - D0728 Ads '88, 1988 (Box 32)
  - D0729 Campaign '88 - NY State, 1988 (Box 32)
  - D0730 Input 88, 1988 (Box 32)
  - D0731 News Tape '88 - Dukakis Bush 1st Debate, 1988 (Box 32)
  - D0732 McNeil - Lehrer - Gephardt, Simon, Dukakis, Jackson, Babbitt, Dole, Kemp, Robertson, Haig, duPont, Bush, 1/28/88 (Box 32)
  - D0733 New Hampshire, Boston '88 Spots, 2/1/88 (Box 32)
  - D0734 Chicago Spots, 3/1/88 (Box 32)
  - D0735 NSG "Biz" Project - CBS EN - NBC NN, 3/4 - 6/88 (Box 32)
  - D0736 Reagan Speech in London, 6/3/88 (Box 32)
  - D0737 Vice Presidential Debate - Bentsen/Quayle, 10/5/88 (Box 32)
  - D0738 88 Campaign / News / Spots / Dukakis Bush 2nd Debate, 10/13/88 (Box 32)
  - D0739 Nightline, 11/16/89 (Box 32)
  - D0740 Chris Nine [?], 3/20/89 (Box 33)
  - D0741 Gromyko Project / GMA / CBS EV / GMA, 9/1/89 (Box 33)
  - D0742 The Eleventh Hour #245 Joseph Campbell, 10/24/89 (Box 33)
  - D0743 Nightline: Berlin Wall, 11/9/89 (Box 33)
  - D0744 Revolution Will Be Televised, 11/12/89 (Box 33)
  - D0745 1990 Election: Bradley, Rowland, Cuomo Commercials (Box 33)
  - D0746 John Kerry for US Senate in 1990 (Box 33)
  - D0747 Jack Cafferty's Newsline NY, 3/14/90 (Box 33)
  - D0748 Can Joe Dolt?, 4/2/90 (Box 33)
  - D0749 TV Coverage About Japan, 11/1/90 (Box 33)
  - D0750 TV Coverage About Japan, 12/1/90 (Box 33A)
  - D0751 TV Coverage About Japan, 1/1/91 (Box 33A)
  - D0752 TV Coverage About Japan, 2/1/91 (Box 33A)
  - D0753 TV Coverage About Japan, 4/1/91 (Box 33A)
  - D0754 TV Coverage About Japan, 5/1/91 (Box 33A)
  - D0755 TV Coverage about Japan, 6/1/91 (Box 33A)
  - D0756 TV Coverage About Japan, 7/1/91 (Box 33A)
  - D0757 TV Coverage About Japan, 8/1/91 (Box 33A)
  - D0758 Edge: Pilot, 8/28/91 (Box 33A)
  - D0759 TV Coverage of Japan, 9/1/91 (Box 33A)
  - D0760 TV Coverage of Japan, 10/1/91 (Box 33A)
  - D0761 20/20, 11/29/91 (Box 33A)
  - D0762 Edge - Show #103, 11/29/91 (Box 33A)
  - D0763 1992 Campaign Ads Incl. UK Conservative Party Broadcast (Box 33A)
  - D0764 Ad Watch - New Hampshire Presidential Primary Ads, 1992 (Box 33A)
  - D0765 Campaign '92, 1992 (Box 33A)
  - D0766 Campaign '92 - Perot - Flipcharts, 1992 (Box 33A)
  - D0767 George Bush Commercials - 800#, 1992 (Box 33A)
  - D0768 Illinois Primary '92 / Locals / Clinton - Tsongas, 1992 (Box 33A)
  - D0769 Interactive Politics - '92 Campaign Highlights Tape A, 1992 (Box 33A)
  - D0770 Interactive Politics - '92 Campaign Highlights Tape B, 1992 (Box 33A)
  - D0771 Ken Swope '92 Demo + Bad Hatkin Spots at End, 1992 (Box 33A)
  - D0772 Presidential Campaign Commercials '92, 1992 (Box 33A)
  - D0773 War Room, 1992; 1st 10 Minutes Missing (Box 33A)
  - D0774 Peter Jennings "Charlie Rose", 5/15/92 (Box 33A)
  - D0775 Hard Copy Shows #790 - 792, 9/25 - 29/92 (Box 33A)
  - D0776 Prez. Debates - JFK/RN '60 - GB/BC/RP, 10/11 - 16/92 (Box 33A)
  - D0777 Elizabeth Johnson - Reporter, 9/1/93 (Box 33A)
  - D0778 60 Minutes, 11/4/93 (Box 33A)
  - D0779 Election Night, 1994 (Box 33A)
  - D0780 Political Ads - Campaign '94, 1994 (Box 33A)
  - D0781 TV Spots (Political Ads) NY, 1994 (Box 33A)
  - D0782 Walt Disney World Trip Promo / Ed Diamond on Today Show / Campaign '94 Spots (Mass.) plus Misc. / C - Span Earl Graves, 1994 (Box 33A)
  - D0783 Today Show - Edwin Diamond, 1/25/94 (Box 33A)
  - D0784 Pozner/Donahue - Guest - Edwin Diamond, 2/27/94 (Box 33A)
  - D0785 Kennedy/Romney Debates / C - Span Campaign Almanac Spots from Around the Country, 10/25 - 27/94 (Box 33)
  - D0786 Equal Time: A History of Women in Broadcast Journalism, 1995 (Box 33)
  - D0787 MTV Interviews - [rest of label unintelligible], 1995 (Box 33)
  - D0788 '96 Campaign Spots / Misc. / Mass. / New England, 1996 (Box 33)
  - D0789 Clinton Bush Political Ad, 1996 (Box 33)
  - D0790 Winning! Best Campaign Commercials of 1996 (Box 33)
  - D0791 Campaign Ad Coverage, 2/9 - 3/4/96 (Box 33)
  - D0792 Campaign Ad Coverage, 9/12/96 (Box 33)
  - D0793 48 Hours Season Premier, 9/12/96 (Box 33)
  - D0794 Primary 1960 / Assorted Cx / Perot Debate, 10/16/96 (Box 33)
  - D0795 Smoke Screen, 11/24/96 (Box 33)
  - D0796 Newstape (Japan) Week of PM, 1/12 - 14/?? (Box 33)
  - D0797 Video News Network, 8/18/?? (Box 33)
  - D0798 State Cx, 10/11/?? (Box 33)
  - D0799 TV Ads Campaign - CNY, 11/5 - 6/?? (Box 33)
  - D0800 Campaign Ads, 11/6 - 7/?? (Box 33)
  - D0801 Election stuff (Box 33)
  - D0802 A Gathering of Men (Box 33)
  - D0803 A Tale of Two Schools (Box 33)
  - D0804 Alissa Wolf (Box 33)
  - D0805 Alton Kite Interview (Covenant House) (Box 33)
  - D0806 Barbara Walter's Special on Ronald Reagan (Box 33)
  - D0807 Bill Moyers: Diary of a Dark Horse - Out of the Reach of Children - Healing and the Mind (Box 33)
  - D0808 Choose or Lose Packages (Box 33)
  - D0809 Comedy of Errors (Box 33)
  - D0810 Cops - One Hour Premiere & First 4 1/2 Hours / 8 min of City Under Siege (Box 33)
  - D0811 Crime Inc. Episode #1 (Box 33)
  - D0812 Crime Inc. Episode #1 (Box 33)
  - D0813 Crime Inc. Episode #1 (Box 33)
  - D0814 Crime Inc. Episode #1 (Box 33)
  - D0815 Crime Inc. Episode #1 (Box 33)
  - D0816 Demo - The Spot (Box 33)
  - D0817 Desert War I & II (Box 33)
  - D0818 Dukakis / Dole / Kemp / Bush / Moynihan / Babbit / Hal Riney (Bear) (Box 33)
  - D0819 Ed Chan. 13 / House Cart / Air War includes Dorsey) / Ed (transit) (Box 33)
  - D0820 Elizabeth Johnson Reporter - (616) 947 - 2711 (Box 33)
  - D0821 Harvest of Shame (Box 33)
  - D0822 Joe Clark: The Myth and the Man (Box 33)
  - D0823 Mabat Israel [rest of label in Hebrew] (Box 33)
  - D0824 Mailer 1 - We Are In Love with the World, Part I / Wiesel I Whatever We Do Must be Measured in Moral Terms / Postman I - Are We Amusing Ourselves to Death?, Part I / Westheimer - Good Sex...with Dr. Ruth (Box 33)
  - D0825 McSorley's New York (Box 33)